thedreamteammovement.com 2017-09-14

# Privacy Policy - Zoom

Updated: 05-12-2017

Zoom Video Communications, Inc. ("Zoom") is committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring you have a positive experience on our website and in using our products and services (collectively "Products"). This policy covers the Zoom website zoom.us, mobile applications, and desktop clients and is applicable worldwide. This policy outlines our handling practices, how we collect and use the personal information you provide through online and offline. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy. This policy may be updated from time to time and our website will indicate when the policy has been updated. You may access the current version at any time by clicking on the "Privacy" link at the footer on our website.

Collection of your personal information

Zoom collects information under the direction of its customers, and, unless a customer is an individual, has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. If you have been contacted by one of our customers and would no longer like to be contacted by that customer using our service, please contact that customer directly. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers of personal data to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our customers.

Described below are situations in which personal information is collected and the purposes for which it is collected. "Personal Information" is any information that can be used to identify an individual, and may include, but is not limited to, name, email address, postal or other physical address, credit or debit card number, title, information generated from use of our Products, and other information required to provide a Product, deliver a product, or carry out a transaction you have requested. Some of the reasons we collect your Personal Information may include:

  * account registration
  * use of certain Product features
  * generating reports based on information collected from use of our Products
  * requesting service and support for our Products and providing such support
  * placing transactions or orders
  * registering to attend a seminar or webinar
  * participating in an online survey
  * submitting an entry for an opt-in sweepstakes or other promotion
  * billing and collecting payments for our Products
  * participating in discussion groups or forums
  * registering for membership programs or newsletter subscriptions
  * customizing the advertising and content you see

Uses of your Personal Information

We will use your Personal Information only in accordance with our Privacy Policy. If you do not wish us to continue using your Personal Information in this manner, you may request that your account be deactivated as specified below. Some of the ways we may use your Personal Information include:

  * To process your orders and deliver the products and Products that you have ordered.
  * To provide reports based on information collected from use of our Products.
  * To keep you up to date on the latest Product announcements, software updates, software upgrades, system enhancements, special offers, and other information, provided that you can edit your marketing preferences at any time as described below.
  * To provide support and assistance for our products and Products.
  * To provide the ability to create personal profile areas and view protected content.
  * To provide the ability to contact you, and provide you with shipping and billing information.
  * To provide customer feedback and support.
  * To provide opt-in contests, sweepstakes or other marketing or promotional activities on the Zoom.us or affiliate websites. Personal Information may be collected to administer those programs.
  * To conduct questionnaires and surveys in order to provide better products and services to our customers and end users. Your completion of any questionnaires is voluntary.
  * To support recruitment inquiries.
  * To understand more about you, so we can personalize newsletters and websites to your preferences. For example, allow you the opportunity to request specific information on products and services that may be of interest.
  * To provide information on your request to another individual such as a friend or co-worker.
  * To meet contract obligations.

Referrals

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our website, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the website. Zoom may store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email [and tracking the success of our referral program]. Your friend may contact us at unsubscribe@zoom.us to request that we remove this information from our database.

Accessing and updating your Personal Information

Zoom may obtain some Personal Information regarding you from Facebook. In order to keep your Personal Information accurate and up to date or to delete any Personal Information, you will need to manage that through your Facebook account. We do not have the ability to modify or delete your Facebook Personal Information.

Upon request Zoom will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by sending an email request to [privacy@zoom.us](mailto:privacy@zoom.us). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

Zoom acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. Except for customers that are individuals, Zoom has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct their query to Zoom's customer (the data controller). If requested to remove data we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.

We may need to retain some Personal Information collected on our site and the Personal Information we process on behalf of our customers for the period of time necessary to provide you service, for legal proceedings, legal requirements or for settling your account, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

Unsubscribing and Opting Out

Each promotional email from Zoom or from third parties to whom Zoom has given your email address with your consent includes instructions on how you can unsubscribe from that category of mailing or from receiving email from that third party.

You may also unsubscribe from Zoom's promotional emails by sending an email, including your name and email address to [unsubscribe@zoom.us](mailto:unsubscribe@zoom.us).

If you have additional questions regarding your disclosure choices and Zoom's policies regarding receipt of promotional email, you may contact Zoom by sending an email with your name and email address to [privacy@zoom.us](mailto:privacy@zoom.us).

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this website and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

Passive Collection

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site.

In addition, by using some of our Products, anonymous network information may be transmitted back to us such as Product usage information. This information is transmitted back to us so we can determine how users are interacting with our Products, to assist us with improving our Products, and to correct any problems that may occur.

Tracking Technologies

We Zoom and our partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level.

Mobile Application

When you download and use our Services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and the device identifier (or "UDID").

We send you push notifications from time-to-time in order to update you about any events or promotions that we may be running. If you no longer wish to receive these types of communications, you may turn them off at the device level. To ensure you receive proper notifications, we will need to collect certain information about your device such as operating system and user identification information.

Geolocation

We collect your location based information for the purpose of [locating a place that you may be searching for in your area]. We will only share this information with our mapping provider for the sole purpose of providing you this service.

We may share your geo-location data with third parties for the purpose of them serving you ads for places (such as restaurants) in your area. If you do not wish to allow us to share your information in this manner please opt-out by contacting us at unsubscribe@zoom.us.

You may opt-out of location based services at any time by editing the setting at the device level or by emailing us at unsubscribe@zoom.us.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell or rent your Personal Information to third parties for marketing purposes unless you have granted us permission to do so.

We may share your Personal Information within Zoom and its affiliated companies and with third party service providers for purposes of data processing or storage.

We may also share your Personal Information with business partners, service vendors, authorized third-party agents or contractors in order to provide a requested Product or transaction, including processing orders, processing credit card transactions, hosting websites, hosting event and seminar registration and providing customer support. We only provide these third parties with the minimum amount of Personal Information necessary to complete/utilize the requested Product or transaction, and the third parties are not permitted to use your Personal Information except for limited purpose of completing/providing the requested Product or transaction.

As required by law, we may respond to subpoenas, court orders, or similar legal process by disclosing your Personal Information and other related information, if necessary; We also may choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

We may collect and possibly share Personal Information and any other additional information available to us in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Zoom's terms of service, or as otherwise required by law.

While navigating Zoom's web site or Products you may be directed to content or functionality that is hosted by a third-party supplier. When information is collected on behalf of Zoom exclusively, Zoom's privacy policy will be referenced and will govern how your information is used. For other, non-Zoom sites or services, the site/service owner's privacy policy will be referenced. You should review such supplier's privacy and security policies prior to use.

We will ask for your consent before we use or share your information for any purpose other than the reason you provided it or as otherwise provided by this policy. In order to let us know your preferences, we will require an action on your part, such as checking the appropriate option, to indicate your consent.

Security of your Personal Information

Zoom is committed to protecting the Personal Information you share with us. We utilize a combination of industry-standard security technologies, procedures, and organizational measures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

When we transfer credit card information over the Internet, we protect it using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology.

We recommend you to take every precaution in protecting your Personal Information when you are on the Internet. For example, change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers when creating passwords, and make sure you use a secure browser.

If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at [privacy@zoom.us](mailto:privacy@zoom.us).

Linked websites and third party services

Our websites and services may provide links to other third-party websites and services which are outside our control and not covered by this policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) sites you visit or services you use.

Newsgroups/forums

If you participate in a Zoom discussion forum or chat room, you should be aware that the information you provide there will be made broadly available to others, potentially inside or outside Zoom, who have access to that discussion forum or chat room. Also, please recognize that individual forums and chat rooms may have additional rules and conditions. Each participant's opinion on a forum or chat room is his or her own and should not be considered as reflecting the opinion of Zoom.

Children's privacy

Zoom does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that data from our systems. Zoom encourages parents and guardians to go online with their children. Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer:

  * Teach children never to give Personal Information (such as name, address, phone number, school, etc.) unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult.
  * Know the sites your children are visiting and which sites are appropriate.
  * Look for website privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated.

Please visit the FTC's website for more tips on protecting children's privacy online.

Consent to Transfer, Processing and Storage of Personal Information

We may transfer your Personal Information to the United States, to any Zoom affiliate worldwide, or to third parties acting on our behalf for the purposes of processing or storage, and by providing any Personal Information you fully understand and unambiguously consent to such transfer, processing and storage of such information.

EU-U.S. Privacy Shield

Zoom (and its parent/subsidiary company(ies)) participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. Zoom is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework's applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's Privacy Shield List. [<https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>]

Zoom is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Zoom complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Zoom is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Zoom may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website [<https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>], you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted. 

Questions or comments?

Should you have any privacy-related questions or comments related to this privacy policy, please send an email to [privacy@zoom.us](mailto:privacy@zoom.us).

Zoom Video Communications, Inc.

Attention: Privacy Officer

55 Almaden Blvd, Suite 600

San Jose, CA 95113

Policy updates

Zoom may amend this privacy statement from time to time, and at any time. We will post a notice on this website whenever this privacy statement is materially changed. Your continued use of the Zoom website or Products after any change will signify and confirm your assent to those changes.
